# for more trivia questions, go to https://opentdb.com/

question_data = [{
    "type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"medium",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
    "correct_answer":"False",
    "incorrect_answers":["True"],
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
     "difficulty":"medium",
     "category":"General Knowledge",
     "question":"Fast food restaurant chains Carl's Jr. and Hardee's are owned by the same company.",
     "correct_answer":"True",
     "incorrect_answers":["False"]
     },
     {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Furby was released in 1998.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"An eggplant is a vegetable.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]